Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place.
That the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary?
Till someone proves it real.
Through it all.
Through all the trouble and times.
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend.
We are, we are on a cruise.
We are.
Ah! My hat! Where's my hat?
It's right there. Calm
down. Oh, good. Here it is.
Have a good nap?
Hey, those pirates!
They're gone now, all thanks to you. Me?
Yeah, and Ginny asked me to tell you
that he said, see you on the Grand Line.
Huh. He did? To you?
No, to you!
So,
I guess I don't have to do any more lame-o
chores since I got those
pirates off your back,
right?
That's the deal.
Hey, I was wondering...
No, I'm not gonna run away
with you to become a pirate.
I've got some unfinished business here.
I'll stay until Zef acknowledges my skill.
Okay, then. I give up.
That means you let go!
I can't just leave.
These bozos don't know the first
thing about how to run a restaurant.
But still, I promised myself that one of
these days, I'll go to the Grand Line.
Well, let's go right now!
It just isn't the right time, not yet.
There is one place.
Say, have you ever heard of the all-blue?
Nuh-uh You've got to be kidding
me That sea is a miracle
In the all-blue there are fish
from the east-blue, the west-blue,
the north-blue, and the south-blue
That one stretch of ocean has it all
To us cooks,
it's a culinary dream
come true A place that
fantastic has got to be on
the Grand Line somewhere,
right?
I mean, where else?
The little Bratman's truly happy.
What an idiot.
All right, guys, soup's on!
Really?
Oh, good.
They saved us some seats. They did?
No chairs left for you.
Just sit on the floor and eat.
There are no chairs?
That doesn't seem right.
This is a restaurant.
All right, fine.
They sure are acting strange.
Well, that's nothing new.
Bunch of jerks.
Hey, what is this?
Who prepared the soup this morning?
Oh, I did.
The stuff is pretty good, huh?
I think I really outdid
myself. Is that a joke?
I can barely hold this slop down!
I thought someone like
you would like slop.
It makes sense to me, seeing
as that's what pigs like. Ha!
Just face it, Sanji, your
soup sucks! It's disgusting!
That soup is nothing short of a delicacy.
There's something wrong
with your taste buds.
Blah, that's gross!
I can't eat this!
Revolting!
This soup is horrible!
What the hell's going on, you bastards?
We're sick of the way you run things.
You're a sham of a sous-chef
and everybody knows it.
You can't just settle every single
little disagreement with violence.
If the food's bad, then
we're gonna say so.
What'd you say?
Boss!
He's her.
That wretched little dish
tasted like stewed garbage.
If we ever served that kind of
trash here, we'd go out of business.
Are you really this stupid?
Just how is my soup any different
from the stuff you make? How?
You think they're the same?
Don't flatter yourself.
The boss punched him.
He didn't kick him.
You think you can lecture me
on the art of cooking, do you?
Fat chance.
I'm a man who has cooked on more seas
than days that you've been alive.
Damn it!
Gah!
What's all the fuss about?
This soup's totally awesome!
All of us know the soup is good.
I know he's an outstanding chef.
Everyone here on the Baratier does.
Yeah, he's great.
Aside from Chef Zef, he's the best we got.
That was scary, wasn't it?
He seriously snapped. Yeah.
But that thick-skulled idiot wouldn't
listen to us if we tried to reason with him.
Hey, listen.
You were saying that you needed
a cook for your ship, right?
Well, this isn't something
I want to be asking anyone,
but would you mind taking that
little brat along with you?
Take him to the Grand Line.
That would be best for him.
The Grand Line is his dream.
Jeez, boss, you sure made
us put on a hell of a show!
Oh, man, I was worried you
was gonna figure it out.
Because of your bad acting.
Come on, your acting
was way worse than mine.
I'm gonna get some more
of that scene, too.
Yeah, that stuff is good.
I can hear everything, you dumbasses.
So what do you say, kid?
No way!
But earlier you mentioned you
needed a cook for your ship.
Just what are you trying to say?
That he's suddenly not
good enough for you?
Oh, he's good.
And I'd love it if he joined
my crew and came with us.
But it seems like he really wants to
stay here and cook with all of you guys.
You can ask me all you want, but
I'm just not going to take him.
So you're saying you can't agree to it
until he tells you himself, is that right?
That's right.
More food, please.
Well, I suppose that's fair enough.
But who knows if that hard-headed little
brat will ever agree to join up with him.
Yeah, once that guy makes up his mind,
there's nothing anybody can do to change it.
More, please!
Sanji, what is that?
A fish man?
Did he come all the way from
Fishman Islands to eat here?
You dolt!
It's a human and a pan shark!
Who's this?
Whoa, it's Yosaku!
Oh, hey, big bro Luffy.
How come you're alone?
Where are the others?
Did you find Nami?
We never actually caught up to her, but
from the direction Big Sis is headed,
we think we've figured out where
she's going and what she plans to do.
I see.
Then we can bring her back.
Maybe.
It's just, if our suspicions
turn out to be true,
then the place she
intends to go could mean
certain death for all
of us if we follow her.
The point is, we really need
your help, Big Bro Luffy.
Please, come with me!
Okay, I don't really get
it, but I got it. Let's go.
Wait.
Your dream is foolish.
Then again, so's mine.
Now is as good a time as any.
Why not start my quest right now?
Sanji?
I'll be joining your little crew on
your journey to be king of the pirates.
You hear me?
I want to be the cook on your
ship. All right. What do you say?
Yeah, of course!
This is great, Big Bro Luffy! Woo-hoo!
We gotta cook!
Now we'll get the tasty food!
Are you guys happy now or what?
Sorry.
Really, I'll leave now.
I don't like it.
To tell you the truth,
I was hoping to give you the boot
from this restaurant personally.
But it seems that you don't have a
problem with straight-up abandoning us
I'm especially sorry for making the lot
of you resort to bad acting. Hey, wait.
How'd you know?
I heard everything you
bunch of jerks. What?
Was stomping on my pride the best
plan that you could come up with
was it you damn geezer Every little
thing has to be a fight with you.
I'm sick and tired of it. Bring it on
Hmm.
I have never liked children
As a matter of fact, I hate children.
There wasn't a day past
when I didn't regret
letting a useless little
brat like you live,
Sanji.
Ha!
Fine by me, you rotten old man.
Enjoy the rest of your miserable life.
Whoa!
This is a nice ship!
You sure it's okay to use her?
Of course.
It's Sanjay's ship.
You still need more? Yep.
Gonna need more meat.
All right.
Well, how many days are
you gonna be out at sea?
I don't know.
It's the nicest sea restaurant
I've ever seen, that's for sure.
Hey, Sanji, listen Huh?
What is it?
It doesn't matter what sort of
person walks through our doors.
If they're hungry, then they will be fed.
Every starving wretch who comes
to us will get a fine meal.
We can make that happen.
It doesn't matter how much we fight.
Because we share the same dream. Ha! Yeah!
Are you ready?
Because we're going to be busy.
You bet!
It won't be a problem with me around.
Awful.
Is that what you call peeling?
That hurt you, old fart.
I'm trying to cook here.
Just stay out of my way and
we won't have any problems.
Got it? What?
You better watch your
mouth, you little brat.
I'm not a little brat,
you crusty old geezer.
Ha! Try this!
Did you make it all by yourself?
Uh-huh!
How is it?
This is the worst soup I've
ever had, you little brat!
You mean old geezer!
Big Bro Cook sure is
taking his time. Yeah.
Now it's payback time!
Here it comes, Sanji!
Really, guys, that was just dumb.
Let's get going.
You don't need to say goodbye?
No, it's fine.
Sanji, take care of yourself, okay?
Chef Sam!
Thanks, you geezer.
I'll never forget your kindness.
I owe my life to you, old man.
So thank you!
You asshole!
I'm gonna miss you so much!
I'll miss you too!
Damn wusses.
Real men should part without a word!
Let alone tears.
Let's go!
Set sail.
I will see you again.
I'll come back someday.
Bye.
Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye.
As long as you sail with enough faith
in yourself, that you have no fear,
not even of death,?
you will find the all-blue.
I'm sure of you.
All right, men.
Customers will be here soon.
Get to work already.
As a kid, I never stopped.
Searching for a great treasure.
I had a map in my mind.
That I knew would lead me.
I had to find my way to that place.
Before someone could beat me.
The promised land was in my grasp.
And I wouldn't let go.
La, la,
la, la, la, I won't stop
chasing it until it comes true.
But if the world ever
changes, I call out your name.
We could return to the time
when everything's the same.
As long as I'm with you,
my memories won't fade.
Waiting for that one true dream?